grammar-monster.com 2014-10-31

# Grammar Monster Privacy Policy

## Grammar Monster's Privacy Policy

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you fill out a form to register for our newsletter. When registering for our newsletter, you will be asked to enter your name and e-mail address.

Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. 

## What do we use your information for?

We use this information to send you periodic emails. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever. You can unsubscribe from our mailing list at any time using the unsubscribe link at the bottom of every email we send. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visit to provide advertisements on our site. 

## How do we protect your information? 

If you complete our registration form, your name and e-mail address are held by our webmail service provider, Bravenet.com. Bravenet.com has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under its control. These measures include secure servers, encrypted passwords, and other security measures to guarantee the privacy of our members. 

## Do we use cookies? 

We do not use cookies. 

## Changes to our Privacy Policy 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes, and update the Privacy Policy modification date below.  

This policy was last modified on 29 August 2014. 

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, you can [contact us using this form](http://www.grammar-monster.com/admin/contact_us.htm).
